Hello Hello, I’m from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsky, where did you understand Moscow from and the World Cup you
Хмельницкий Вы откуда Москва понял а ЧМ
communicate here Yes, about everything about everything and about
общаетесь тут Да обо всём обо всём и ни
nothing I
о чём
understand let’s talk about everything and about nothing let’s let’s start let
понял пообщаемся тоже обо всём и ни о
’s start yes What’s
давайте давайте начинайте начинаю да Что
written on your
написано у вас на
T-shirt Well, in translation that  this
футболке Во так а в переводе что это
means a smart person solves problems and a
означает умный человек решает проблемы а
competent person avoids them avoids
грамотный человек их избегает избегает
cool right Yes they are good wisely
прикольно правильно Да хороши мудро
very realistically I agree and what do you
очень реально согласен а а вы как вообще
think about us What are you doing I’m talking here with
что нам Что делаете Общаюсь тут с
Russians about the war I’m arguing I’m swearing they’re
россиянами о войне спорю ругаюсь
swearing Not if there are some rednecks
матюкаются Не если есть какие-то быдла
There they yell at them  I can Matyuk Well, you are
Там они орут на них могу Матюк Ну вы
normal intellectuals, why are you
нормальные интеллигенты что на вас
swearing like it’s interesting to
матюка типа с вами вот интересно
talk to you, so explain to me both why
поговорить так объясните мне оба зачем
you are going to chat roulette and she
вы собираетесь в чат рулетка и она
By the way, she’s here for the first time today Oh I came
Кстати она первый раз сегодня здесь О я
here for the first time today Wait,
е сегодня прил сюда первый раз Подожди
my name is Andrey What’s your guys name
меня зовут Андрей Вас как зовут ребята
Anastasia's name is Vlad Anastasia Vlad
Анастасия именя Влад Анастасия Влад
Anastasia I correctly understood that you
Анастасия Я правильно понял что ты
came to visit Vlad and he brought you
пришла в гости к Владу и он тебя привёл
to chat roulette. And we have been living
в чат рулетку А мы живём
together for how many 5 years
вместе сколько 5 лет
already
уже
and after 5 years. That is, you decided
и после 5 лет То есть вы решили
to bring something extreme into your
привнести что-то экстремальное в свою
life, yes Well, sort of  today, yes, so
жизнь да Ну типа того сегодня да такая
Vlad really likes to sit in chat roulette, I
Влад очень любит сидеть в чат рулетках я
understand, and he and he decided to bring his wife or
понял да и он и он решил жену там или
girlfriend there Yes, bring him to
девушку Да привезти в
chat roulette He communicates on political
чат-рулетку Он общается на политические
topics I don’t
темы Я не
understand, did you do this meaningfully,
понимаю ты осмысленно сделал это действи
or were you forced Blink not meaningfully,
или тебя заставили Моргни не осмысленно
I’m interested  I’m here against my
мне интересно это я тут против своей
will, look Anastasia, uh, let’s say this,
воли смотрите Анастасия мне э скажем так
I understand why he’s on chat roulette. I
я понимаю зачем он сидит в чат рулетке Я
don’t understand why he decided to show you
не понимаю зачем он вам решил показать
why he’s on chatroulette. I don’t
Зачем он сидит в чатрулет Я тоже не
understand either. Explain this is the most
понимаю Объясните вот вот это самый
incomprehensible question; in short,
непонятный вопрос короче вот неправильно
we’re starting the dialogue wrong  we
мы диалог начинаем мы с самого начала
put me in an awkward position right
меня в неловкое положение ставим прямо
away from the very beginning No, I just wanted to introduce the person
сразу Не ну просто я хотел человека
to what I’m
просто познакомить с тем что мне
interested in, let’s say for example I love
интересно допустим вот к примеру Я люблю
football I say Come with me to football
футбол Я говорю Пойдём со мной на футбол
She likes it I say let’s go to
Она идёт ей нравится Я говорю пойдём в
chat roulette I  I’ll show you what’s
чат-рулетку я тебе покажу что там
going on there, I have an
происходит у меня знакомый У меня
acquaintance I have an acquaintance, Fisherman, so he never
знакомый Рыбак так он никогда же не
thought of showing maggots, for example, he
опарыша не додумался показывать например
says Look, in short, here I am catching sch Yes,
говорит Смотри короче вот я ловлю щ Да
for example, no, well, chat roulette is
например не ну чат рулетка вообще не
not even close at all Well, yes, because you
близко даже не А ну да потому что вы
see Ukrainians with me  there’s a little bit of a
украинцы видите у меня немножко тут
different contingent
другой контингент
coming out here, I didn’t take the
вылазит я девушку не повёл вле ку
Russian girl to see
российскую посмотреть там
the pics there, it’s not really hard, you can see a lot of it,
пиц не на самом деле жести много можно
of course, there’s objectively a lot of it with
увидеть конечно её объективно много с
If you are fans of such extreme
Если Вы любители таких экстремальных
perversions Yes, I advise you, you know what to do,
извращений Да я вам советую знаете что
hang up the flag of Ukraine and
сделайте повесьте флаг Украины и
walk around, choose Russia, the girl is real
походить выберите Россию девушка реально
you're awesome, I came in, I came in with the flag of
офигеете заходил заходил заходи с флагом
Ukraine Yes, just like that on the wall so that it hangs Well,
Украины Да вот так на стене чтобы висел
no, yes, such returns I definitely won’t
А ну нет да таких возвращения Я точно не
get there like that That’s when the girl The maximum
дойду так вот Вот тогда деву Максимум
that I’m ready The maximum that I’m ready is
что я готов Максимум что я готов - это
to install a VPN but I’m impressed Yes, she
VPN поставить но ре впечатлена Да она
will be so
будет скажем настолько
enthusiastic, let’s say  understand who is in front of you and you
воодушевлением понять кто перед вами а
will already hear just a whole stream of
уже будете слышать прям целый поток
imperial conduct, not by the way, I wouldn’t
имперского вели не кстати не я бы не
say there are no deer, there are real ones,
сказал не олени есть встречаются реально
but right without exception there, conventionally call
но прям поголовно там условно называть
everyone there, notorious there, conventionally there,
там каждого там отъявленный там условно
some kind of clown or a fool, well,
там клоуном каким-то или дурачком ну
hardly No, I don’t even  when yesterday or
вряд ли Нет я даже когда вчера или
the day before yesterday, in my opinion, I came in with a
позавчера по-моему заходил с ну с
Ukrainian, with a Ukrainian
украинским этим с украинским
pin, there were a lot of
пином много было с российской стороны
quite adequate guys on the Russian side and now there are
достаточно адекватных ребят и сейчас там
Normal Ukrainians. I’m just saying to me,
украинцев Нормальных Я говорю Просто мне
well, here you are, Vadim, it’s clear. That is,
как бы ну вот вы Вадим понятно То есть
you yourself are from Donetsk. Well, that is
вы сами из Донецка родом Ну то есть у
it hurts you that's why you're in chat roll No
вас это болит поэтому вы в чат рулет Нет
why Donetsk Why Donetsk Moscow You're not
почему Донецк Почему Донецк Москва Вы не
from Donetsk
из Донецка
No you're Vadim Vlad that I was mistaken It
Нет вы Вадим Влад что я ошибся Мне
seemed to me that it means I communicated with another check Yes, it
казалось это значит другим чеком общался
would all be different Yes I mean something for the
бы всё это друго другое Да я так
first time  I see Yes, I understand
что-то я первый раз значит вижу Да понял
Yes, you just want to bet that you don’t
Да просто вам хочется поспорить вам не
have enough male drive Kato Yes, but
хватает зна Като мужского драйва Да но
it’s very extreme for a girl to drive
девушку это очень экстремально водить
a roulette How many people
рулетку Сколько уже человек
have already been taken out today yes Well,
вынули м сегодня да
I think that somewhere probably That’s it, I
А ну я думаю что где-то наверное Вот
probably talked to about five people
именно пообщался наверное человек пять
Well, it’s just not normal  not with
вот Ну прямо нормально не не с
Anastasia that Anastasia saw directly
Анастасией что Анастасия видела прямо
the conversations of about five people, probably Five Well,
разговоры человек пять наверное Пять Ну
that’s already a lot Well, I recommend if it’s
это уже много Ну Я рекомендую если
the first time and no more on the first day no
первый раз да не больше в первый день не
more than three talk to him give her chat
больше трёх разговор ему ей давать чат
roulette yes, in fact,
рулетки да на самом деле недооцениваете
you underestimate her, she actually has a mental state
вы её у неё на самом деле психика очень
you are very stable,
устойчивая вы кто по образованию
Anastasia is a
Анастасия
psychologist by training, look, you can
психолог вот а смотри Вы можете
use chat roulette, you know from the point of
использовать чат-рулетку знаете с точки
view of scientific interest. Well, by the way, yes,
зрения научного интереса Ну да Вот
you have a boyfriend who is an economist by
кстати да у Вас парень кто по
training.
образованию
Anastasia, you Then you need to
экономист Анастасия вам Тогда нужно
figure out why your boyfriend is
разобраться Почему Ваш парень вместо
now thinking like  earn money
того чтобы сейчас думать как заработать
Yes, he sits and does his Ph.D.
бабки Да сидит и занимается кандидатской
thesis on psychology in chat roulette
диссертацией по психологии в чат рулетке
And by the way, I’ll answer in reality Why let’s, let’s There is
А кстати отвечу на самом деле Почему
such an expression, by the way, I don’t remember who By the way,
Есть такое выражение кстати не помню кто
maybe even Hitler By the way, he
Кстати может даже Гитлер Кстати это
said that firstly, when
сказал что во-первых тогда когда
diplomacy ends,
заканчивается дипломатия начинается
war begins, secondly, money is earned then
война второе деньги зарабатываются тогда
when blood flows, this is what Ignatius said
когда течёт кровь это Игнатий ла говорил
probably Well, from the Jesuit Order, that
вероятно Ну из Ордена иезуитов то что
he led the Inquisition Yes, and with regards to money
инквизицией руководил Да и касаемо денег
and blood Work history, how
и крови Рабочая история как бы это
bone-chilling it sounds, even if we take, say, the
костно звучало даже если брать допустим
Moscow Exchange index Yes, over the
там индекс Московской биржи Да за
last year, plus there are
последний год плюс там
70-80 people who invest there
70-80 люди которые там инвестируют свои
In general, they earn their money quite well No
деньги в целом зарабатывают неплохо Как
matter how terribly it sounds,
бы это не звучало ужасно там
blasphemous and
кощунственно и так
so on, therefore, to understand in general what is
далее поэтому понимать в целом то что
happening, I don’t
происходит не
know somewhere, even to see and hear the
знаю где-то даже видеть и слышать
opposite
противоположную
side. I’m interested in this, in
сторону Мне это интересно я на самом
fact, they said that come Yes, I’m  It’s
деле вот сказали том что приходите Да я
not about arguing there, insulting
т не про то что поругаться там оскорбить
someone, it’s not interesting to me at all
кого-то мне это не интересно абсолютно
because there’s no point in it.
потому что толку от этого нет никакого
I’m interested in really hearing and understanding the
Мне интересно реально услышать и понять
opposite side. Let’s
противоположную сторону Вот давайте
hear the opposite side. The
услышите противоположную сторону
opposite side asks one
противоположное сторонам вопрошает один
simple question: why did you go kill
простой вопрос зачем вы полезли убивать
people in Ukraine and die?
людей в Украине и умирать
themselves
сами
Geopolitics
Геополитика
future
будущее
change in the global world order in
изменение глобального мира порядка в
general what is happening now is not not
целом то что сейчас происходит это не не
history Anastasia he is for you too You when
история Анастасия он вам тоже Вы когда
Tell him Listen dear When we
Говорите ему Слушай милый Когда мы
go to the sea and he is like the
поедем на море а он такой
sun the beach
солнце пляж
happens like this
бывает бывает такое
yes let me repeat the question again okay
да давайте ещ раз повторю вопрос
why did you attack  to Ukraine, you kill
лад зачем вы напали на Украину убиваете
people here and die yourself. Well, look
тут людей и умираете сами Ну смотрите
formally. We stood up for the Republics,
формально Мы вступились за Республики
which we
которые мы и
recognized, for example. Let's Republics of
признали например Давайте Республики
non-people, we protect people, we protect the
нере людей защищаем людей защищаем
Kherson and Zaporozhye regions, who are you
Херсонской и Запорожской области кого вы
defending? There were no republics there. By the way,
защищаете там не было никаких республик
Lavrov, by the way, interestingly said
кстати Лавров кстати интересно сказал
about this story just like that  with regards to the
про эту историю как раз вот касаемо вот
question regarding why it goes beyond the
вопроса касаемо того почему сходит за
scope of those Well, the regions there for
рамки и вот тех Ну регионов там за
which we entered And from where does the
которые мы вступали А оттуда Откуда
aggression come in our direction, in any
приходит агрессия в нашу сторону в любом
case there will be blows there and there
случае будут там наноситься удары и
will be further blows And why, look,
будет поте удары А зачем вот смотрите
blows are not blows
удары не удары
Why did they proclaim that Kherson is
Зачем провозгласили что херсонское
Zaporozhye  the region is part of the
Запорожской область - это часть
Russian Federation now Why was
Российской Федерации теперь Почему
n’t the Sumy region declared or the Kharkov
сумскую не провозгласили или харьковскую
region taken over by the Kherson Zaporozhye
область взяли вот херсонскую запорожскую
By the way, the question is why I wouldn’t
Вот кстати вопрос почему вот я бы не
mind, by the way, if the Sumy region was also
против был кстати чтобы сумскую тоже
probably
наверное
annexed, the
присоединили
question is why only them. Come on,
вот вопрос почему только их А давайте
Anastasia, don’t you think that your guy
Анастасия вам не кажется что ваш парень
is he’s moral?  a
Он моральная [__]
bit of a bastard Look, he goes to chat
немножко Вот смотрите Он выходит в чат
roulette, he knows that his country is killing
рулетку он знает что его страна убивает
people in my country, he goes to chat
людей в моей стране он выходит в чат
roulette, he chooses Ukrainians, and he
рулетку выбирает украинцев Да и
mocks me, and I would take more money there, and
издевается а я бы ещё суммы там забрал и
so on. Do you think this is worthy of
так дальше Как вы считаете это достойно
a man? Well, you do the same  most no,
мужчины Ну вы же делаете тоже самое нет
I and you, by the way, are provocative, very
я а вы кстати провокационно очень
one-sided, provocative questions, just
однобокий провокационные вопросы ещ
wait, don’t interrupt Anastasia, I
подождите не перебивайте Анастасию я с
talked to you. I’m your country, too,
вами поговорил Я вот ваша страна тоже
killing our soldiers, where we kill those
убивает наших солдат где мы убиваем тех
who came to attack us. Absolutely
которые пришли к нам нападать Абсолютно
right, you choose Russia in order to
верно вы выбираете Россию для того чтобы
conflict and swear. No, I  I choose
конфликтовать И ругаться Нет я выбираю
Russia because Russia came to my country, so
Россию потому что в моей стране пришла
let’s by the way, no, she
Россия пото Давайте кста можно Нет она
didn’t pass you, I clearly understood your position
не перевала вас я чётко вашу позицию
and I want to see how Anastasia
понял и хочу посмотреть как Анастасия
thinks about your position, don’t influence
думает про вашу позицию не влияете
her answer now because she, as a
сейчас на её ответ потому что она как
psychologist, understands that she must
психолог понимает что она должна сама
give the answer herself  and not under your
дать ответ а не под вашим
influence, I’m interested, yes, look at the
влиянием мне интересно да смотрите
question Yes, we didn’t attack Russia, and we didn’t
вопрос Да не мы напали на Россию да не
come to Russia to kill Russians, but the
мы приходим в Россию убивать россиян а
Russians came to Ukraine to kill
россияне пришли в Украину убивать
Ukrainians, so when a Russian
украинцев поэтому когда россиянин
comes into the chat, what about 2014, what
выходит в чату А как же 2014 год что
where did we come to Russia to kill Who?  Well,
куда мы в Россию пришли убивать Кого Ну
there were a lot of Russian people killed. Where
было очень много русских людей убита Где
where were they killed? Wait again, look again, we are
где убита Подождите ещё раз смотрите мы
Ukraine, what happened in Ukraine now we
Украина что было в Украине сейчас мы
can talk, but not a single
можем поговорить но в Россию ни один
Ukrainian soldier and no one
украинский солдат и никто никого не
came to Russia to kill anyone; it’s
убивать не приходил
true. Perhaps we don’t know for sure. Well, we
правда Возможно мы не знаем наверняка Ну
don’t know for sure. Well.  for Well, I just have
как наверняка не знаем Ну за Ну я просто
n’t been to that’s how where in Russia, well, how
не была на вот как куда в Россию ну как
would we go into Russia, well, can you imagine
мы зашли бы в Россию ну представляешь
Russia has such a strong border guard And that’s it And
Россия такая сильная погранвойска И всё
we came, like, to kill someone there in
И мы пришли типа кого там убить в
Rostov, or that
Ростове или что вот
we didn’t originally come to
мы первоначально не приходили вас
kill you, we originally had  And
убивать у нас первоначально же была И
now there is a special military operation going on,
сейчас идёт специальная военная операция
operation military military does not
операция военная военная не
mean to
подразумевает
kill military operation does not
убивать военная операция не
mean military means to
подразумевает означает воен означает во
destroy strategically
уничтожить стратегически
important military don’t wait wait people
важные военна не подожди подожди людей
not people understood that is, it’s just, well, things
не людей понял то есть просто ну дело
have gone too far it’s gone too
зашло слишком далеко дело зашло слишком
far Got it Look, imagine
далеко Понял Вот смотрите представляете
such a situation that  Well, it’s getting even worse.
такую ситуацию что ну и дело ещё больше
Far away, can you imagine? What,
доходит Далеко да представляете Что
for example,
например
next year already Yes, for example, you are
э в следующий год уже Да например вы
celebrating your birthday there on June 9
себе там празднуете 9 июня день рождения
Yes, Vlad is celebrating, and
Да Влада празднуете а
then the military commissar knocks on the door and
потом стучится в дверь военком и
says, you know,
говорит знаешь
Kaliningrad is
Калининград тебя
calling you, you need to defend your
зовёт нужно защитить
homeland somewhere near Zaporozhye because  that
родину где-то под Запорожье потому что
those whom we mobile Zro last year
тех кого мы мобили Зро в прошлом году
they already died Yes, son, it’s sad, but
они уже сдохли Да сынок это печально но
this is a
это
war, don’t get involved, how would you
война не включайтесь как бы вы
react to what Vlad
да отреагировали на что Влада
was beaten to death, for example, well,
прибили под бахмут например
you definitely wouldn’t have caused any joy, but
ну радости бы ты точно не вызвала но
well, we switched, hello,
а ну переключились здравствуйте
just Like and write  and
а просто Поставьте лайк пишиться и
fill out the comment so cool write on th
залиште коментар це було круто пись на й
Telegram directly at the same time axis VN
Telegram прямо зараз ось ВН
apok so much more and more important YouTube keeping
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us busy through skarg or in twy ban and even
нас через скарг ор в твий бан и дуже
more videos I don’t show people constantly I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams That’s why
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we need Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
write directly immediately and while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm sche tezh
окм
tsikava and korisna information and we are
ще теж цикава и корисна информация и мы
responsible for you trimati postiyny
повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational link
оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukrai
YouTube Слава украи
pis
пись